[Music]
all right guys so if you guys asked in
the last video if you guys wanted to see
how I mark off my air of Interest I got
a plus load of comments so if you guys
haven't seen the last video make sure to
go check it out thanks to me marking off
these areas of Interest the right way I
was able to make 60k day on gold 50k a
day on GJ all these huge days which I
was able to buy myself another Richard
Mill so shout out to TPT for hooking it
up and as I'm buying the Richard Mill
I'm seeing these Iced Out Rolexes and
I'm thinking to myself shout out to
Sensei this guy lent me the years for
two weeks because I'm in between about
buying a year sir cuddling and he's
always wanted an i style Rolex so I
bought him a two-tone I style Rolex
which is crazy I've never gifted anybody
anything as crazy as this so make sure
you watch the video I'm going to be
gifting him the Rolex in this video and
I'm going to be giving you guys the
three very key important tips on how to
find these area of Interest the correct
way so check it
alright guys so the first things before
you find your area of interest you need
to understand whether we're bullish or
bearish are we bullish on the weekly are
we bearish on the weekly what is going
on with the time frame so in order for
me to sell first things first before
finding any area of Interest I need to
understand what is the market doing and
I do not take any trade unless we have
two time frames in sync I'm going to
show you exactly what I mean by that
right now as you can tell here the
weekly time frame is clearly bearish
we're creating lower low lower high
lower low now we're creating a potential
lower high to create a lower low so this
is where we would type off the weekly
time frame is bearish next would be the
date this we would go to the Daily time
frame we understand what is the daily
doing are we bullish embarrassed so in
this case we understand that the daily
is creating lower low lower high no no
then we shifted here to creating higher
highs and higher lows again if you guys
want to know more details about Market
structure have a three-day accelerated
boot camp just click the link below and
another way to tell how this Market
shifted from bearish to bullish we had
here an inverted head and shoulders
right so now that we understand that the
weekly time frame I mean the daily time
frame is bullish we'll just type that up
now we would go down to the four hour we
need to know whether the weekly daily or
four hour what are the trends doing so
it's going to go down to the four hour
and we could sell at the four hour time
frame is bearish we were creating here
higher highs and higher lows again I'm
skipping a lot of structure here just to
keep it simple uh higher low higher high
and then we've broken structure here
making this time frame now bearish so
now we understand that the majority of
these time frames is to the downside so
we add here the Confluence we have four
hour Bears meaning we have two time
frames in sync to the downside so now
there's no reason why you should be
taking Longs obviously the majority of
the market is going down so this is my
first point understand what is the
market doing are we bullish bearish and
we need a minimum of two time per is in
sync to take the trade now my next point
is going to be how to find the area of
Interest all right so I just got this
watch right if you can guess how much
this watch is worth I'll give you 100
bucks it's G-Shock
uh but it's like 20K let's say 200 huh
twenty thousand sure 100
all right so now in the next point is
finding your air Adventure so obviously
we're bearish on the weekly and bearish
number four hours so we're looking to
sell I'm not looking to buy because
simply the conferences aren't that much
right if I say you were to take this as
a grade for me and everybody in the
guide to bootcamp
um we were greatest a 20 towards
yourself because it's 10 per time frame
anything lower than the four hour to me
is just not strong I don't use it as a
Confluence whether to understand what
we're but there's we use it for other
things but that's in a completely other
video
um so for this case when we understand
that we need to sell at a weekly area of
interest because again keep in mind we
are bearishing the weekly so we need to
sell based off of the weekly so this is
where we would mark off our lower high
and our lower low so this should be our
lower high point right here again if you
guys want to do another video on lower
high and lower low which is pretty
simple make sure to drop a comment so
this is the lower high and then this
would be the lower low so we understand
we're only looking for areas of interest
within this box so a little hack that I
do is I would Zone it off like this and
then I know I'm looking for areas of
interest to sell within this box I'm
looking for retracement somewhere in
here to install if you break out of this
box we are now bullish we're no longer
looking to sell a big common mistake
people would do they come onto the
markets they'll mark this off oh yeah
this is a strong level of resistance so
is this area right here it's used as
support and resistance yes and it's a
fact this is a clean level of support
resistance support resistance but if
price gets to that point right there
we're no longer Birch we're no longer
looking for cells so that's what makes
it in value that's why it's so important
how to properly mark up these lower
highs and lower lows so I would start
off looking for areas of interest from
the bottom up and I pretty much look for
whatever points have the most touches in
this case it is around psychological 66
500 and if you look left that it's a
very well respected level of support and
resistance so so now I know how I'm
looking to sell at this area so let's
say that price wouldn't be around here I
would have to wait for price to get to
this area in order for me to be
interested in sales so all of this time
price is on the way there we're just we
just set it forget just pretty much just
wait until the price gets there so now
on my next point is what do I do once
price gets to this area of Interest
which is pretty much basically how you
enter the trade so stay tuned to the
next Point all right so we just pulled
up to census house and we're going to
give him a box of shoes because he
actually gave me these guccis it was
random one day he was like yo here's a
happy shoe that I'm like okay I don't
have a pair of Gucci so now we're going
to give him the shoebox thinking I'm
gonna give him a shoe but inside we have
the uh the Rolex hitting up so let's
wait for him to put I remember when this
guy came to Miami without knowing a
single word of English and he had
nothing to his name seen him build from
the ground up is insanely motivational
to me kind of like my story had nothing
working at Duncan and we both build up
great success so the fact that I'm not
only am I able to have success myself
but share with others literally means
the world to me like look at the look at
this reaction that he gets now when he
sees the watch he's always wanted so
that's my goal for the rest of my life
is to give back give back to all of you
guys whether it's as friends advice
YouTube videos education three days it's
an early boot camp guided boot camp
whatever it is my goal is to give you
guys transfer all of this success that I
have to you guys so you guys can one day
be in a position how Sensei and I are
but check out how he grabs my waist
right now kind of sucks
all right guys now after you have marked
off your area of Interest this is where
you would go down to the lower time
frames to enter a trade right so in
order for you to sell this is super
important and I mean they're all very
important but it's probably like the key
to your entry signal or entry tactic
whatever you want to call it if you're
looking to sell you need to sell at a
lower high if you're looking to buy you
need to buy at a higher low do not let
this go over your head again if you need
to sell you need to sell at a lower high
or a potential lower high and if you're
looking to buy you need to buy at a
higher low potential higher look so this
is where you would go down to the four
hour and I need to have a four hour
lower high to sell so as you can tell in
this case once we approach our area of
interest for the first time wins we've
got here there was absolutely no lower
high everything was simply higher high
if you want to call this a higher low
which I wouldn't so we'll just keep it
going this is a higher low this is
Harlow and notice how we've broken
through the area of Interest breaking
through it not giving us a lower high at
any point so this is where we would wait
for the break of the structure which
would give us a lower note so as you can
tell right here we've had the break of
structure if we were to call this our
higher low this would be a high high
here we broke it giving us now a lower
high and I say we don't take this trade
for whatever reason this is where you
would then wait for the next lower note
to happen and now is when you would wait
for a lower high then you would get a
retest of 6500 read system air
adventures in the weekly retest the four
hour EMA reaches the neckline of the
head and shoulders so if you notice you
have abundance of conferences by just
waiting for the shift of the structure
this is going to make or break your
trade and for me when this trade plays
out very soon it would be a b setup B
plus you know the way we grade it in the
three-day accelerated boot camp it's
based off of percentages you give your
trade so this right here would be a
perfect prime example of what I would be
looking to sell as you can tell now we
have a lower high and our area of
Interest rejection from all these points
so this is where you would wait now for
your entry signal and then pretty much
wait for the proper session to take the
train so if you found all these tips
useful but just subscribe to the channel
I give away free supplies all the time
make sure to subscribe and I'll see you
guys in the next video